https://www.silvon.com/privacy.php

Stratum for JDE
Stratum for Infor XA (MAPICS)
Stratum for Infor LX (BPCS)
Stratum for Infor PRMS
Stratum for Infor DISTRIBUTION (SX.e, FACTS, A+)
Typical Evolution
Why Stratum ?
Typical Evolution
Why Stratum?
Stratum for JDE
Stratum for Infor XA (MAPICS)
Stratum for Infor LX (BPCS)
Stratum for Infor PRMS
Stratum for Infor DISTRIBUTION (SX.e, FACTS, A+)
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE COLLECT IT
In general, you can visit this web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.
There are times, however, when we may need information from you.
Personal information like your name, postal address and e-mail address is obtained only when voluntarily submitted.
Silvon collects this information in several ways:
Through registration, surveys and other online forms
As part of an ongoing sales process
While providing technical support, consultation, or product information
Through the process of maintaining and upgrading our products
Through automated means such as communications protocols, e-mail communications and cookies
To provide you with timely, high-quality information, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your professional interests and experiences with our products or services.
Providing us with this information is optional.
Personal data collected online may also be combined with information you provide to us through other sources such as product registration, call centers, or in conjunction with events such as trade shows, training seminars and conferences.
Information that you supply will relate to the relationship that Silvon has with you or your organization.
INFORMATION ABOUT COOKIES, AND ABOUT GOOGLE ANALYTICS AND LEADLANDER
Cookies are very small text files stored on your computer by your web browser. This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. and LeadLander which both use javascript and cookies to help us analyze how visitors use the site.
You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. If cookies are refused, you will still be able to use our website, and anonymous data will still be collected in our internal transaction logs. By accepting cookies, you consent to the processing of data in the manner and for the purposes set out in this privacy notice.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
Silvon may use your personal information to:
Fulfill subscription requests, orders for software and services made online and to provide other information you request
Make the Web site easier for you to use
Help us customize content most relevant to your interests
Notify you about important news concerning Silvon
Notify you of new products and services, product updates, technical support issues, events and special offers we think you may be interested in
We do analyze some of our Web services such as registrations, demos, downloads, and e-mail responses at the individual level in order to improve the quality of those offerings and to better tailor our marketing to our customers' needs.
HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
We will not sell, rent or lease to others your personally identifiable information.
Silvon reserves the right to disclose any and all pertinent information to law enforcement or other governmental officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS
By using Silvon's Web site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Statement.
INFORMATION CORRECTION AND DELETION
If you believe that any information we have about you in incorrect, you are welcome to contact us so we can update it and keep your data accurate.
Any data that is no longer needed will be deleted immediately afterwards.
If at any point you wish for Silvon Software to delete information about you, simply contact us at info@silvon.com.
HOW TO CONTACT US
Should you have comments or questions about this Privacy Statement, you may e-mail
us at:
info@silvon.com.
You may also contact us via postal mail at the following address:
Silvon Software Inc.
900 Oakmont Lane,
Suite 301,
Why Stratum?
Technology
Free Trial
Industry Solutions
Stratum for JDE
Stratum for Infor XA (MAPICS)
Stratum for Infor LX (BPCS)
Silvon Software Inc. 900 Oakmont Lane, Suite 301, Westmont, IL 60559
• 800 874 5866
• Fax: 630 655 3377 •
info@silvon.com
• HOME
Copyright ® 2020 Silvon Software Inc. All rights reserved. Our Privacy Policy
